Viewers, whatever spirit that is causing you nightmares, failure, setback, barrenness -
I curse them in the name of Jesus!
Be released!
You spirit, leave my people!
Loose your grip, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, whatever medium you are using to view us right now,
all are given right.
You are made to overcome by the word of your confession.
I mean, mean it - whatever you say!
Confess right now all your sickness and disease.
I separate you, in the name of Jesus from that disease in your organs!
Wherever it is located - that infirmity in your organ -
wherever it is located - I say, "Be healed!"
Be delivered!
Be healed!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, I can see you being healed.
He sent forth His Word and healed them.
He is the same yesterday, today and forever.
His Word never changes.
I send His Word from my heart to you:
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Begin to flush out every infirmity by the blood of Jesus and the power of the Holy Ghost.
By the power of the Holy Ghost and the blood of Jesus, begin to flush it out wherever it is located.
Flush it out!
In the name of Jesus!
Viewers, whatever medium you are using to view us at this moment,
I strengthen your faith.
I pray your faith will not fail.
Faith heals now.
Faith delivers now.
Faith receives now.
Faith blesses now.
Receive now!
Be delivered now!
In Jesus Christ's name!